{
    "id": "8e1a43396f1347f09dee2cf66dfab35f",
    "title": "Present Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My father …………………. for a walk in the morning. (Habitual action)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "goes",
                "is going"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9b7ac5e02b564565a2a83def16a48045"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. coffee in the morning. (Habitual action)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drink",
                "drinks",
                "am drinking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1393b18431a34e01a773f401cc29c277"
        },
        {
            "question": "Flowers ..................... in the spring. (Fact)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bloom",
                "blooms",
                "are blooming"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07ef30f6ce2745a5bc9cdd92c34ba830"
        },
        {
            "question": "Birds ..................... their nests in trees. (General truth)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "makes",
                "make",
                "are making"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "64a1caef9ecd4b3e985651348cf7a70c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The pigeon .....................… the art of nest-making.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not know",
                "do not know",
                "does not know"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "acc6cd170b40427780a01df55907e8bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Deciduous trees .....................… their leaves in the autumn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shed",
                "sheds",
                "shedding"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e03ff16c6d1c4567b50381c85ff4ddcc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody ...................... dishonest people. (Fact)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "likes",
                "is liking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "217c2668d74f4f299c671bbc4f14a83f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter .....................…… in a factory.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "works",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc27d6bdbb1f4182865107619d47ae30"
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister ..................... . abroad. (Fact)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "is living"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a3475273e204b148a882242171c6081"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... .. best in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "works",
                "am working"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "db4523e511284f56b115a504f1bb514a"
        }
    ]
}